

SOFTWARE ENGINEER



Full stack developer mainly back-end oriented with more than 4 years of experience. Computer enthusiast from an early age and constantly checking the latest technologies, I have learned to code in many programming languages. I am a person who thrives in challenges that's why I always try to bring new ideas to improve the context of a mission/product.



LinkedIn in/williamdhenin/

Phone 06 30 08 57 69



EDUCATION

Software and Math. Engineer INP-ENSEEIHT, Toulouse

2014 - 2017

CPGE - PSI

Lycée Saliège, Balma

2012 - 2014

Scientific A-level (Math option) Lycée Déodat de Séverac, Toulouse 2011

QUALITIES

- Autonomous
- Multi-skilled
- Rigorous
- Team spirit

LANGUAGES

French Mother tongue

Fluent (TOEIC 920) **English**

Spanish Medium

MISCELLANEOUS











Video **Editing**

WORK EXPERIENCE

Since 2021 •

Software Engineer - Tech. Lead Sopra Steria, Colomiers

Leading the development of multiple web applications .NET / Sharepoint / Java

2019 - 2021

Software Engineer C#.NET - Tech. Lead Capgemini, Toulouse

- Maintenance and development (full stack) of the management system for assistance in the diagnosis and maintenance of the Rafale aircraft engine. (« Fat » Client)
- Adapting the system to the implementation of the application for export including Egypt, India and Qatar

2016 - 2019

Software Engineer C#.NET - Tech. Lead Capgemini, Toulouse

- Development of applications (full stack) in a context of rapid development in agile and distributed mode as well as thirdparty application maintenance of an application set.
- Apprenticeship from 2016 to 2017
- Technical team supervision (5 persons) as technical lead from

Summer 2015

Internship – Android Developer DriverNet, Manchester, Angleterre

Development (full stack) of an Android application for a startup intended to be used by drivers in order to help them for their deliveries

SKILLS & TOOLS

JavaScript/TypeScript • • • ○ ○

C# .NET Java/JEE • 0 HTML5/CSS3 SQL Oracle 000

Web-Services/REST Jenkins • • 0 0 Docker Angular 2+ GIT GraphQL 000